we are all people we make mistakes we screw
todos somos personas nos equivocamos la
up we have friends that we don't
cagamos tenemos amistades que no nos
get along with we don't get along badly but
llevamos bien no nos llevamos mal pero
don't judge people because you don't
no enjuicie a las personas porque os
get along with other people It's not
llevéis mal con otras personas No es
fair and if you think about it inside it
justo y si lo pensáis bien para dentro
's not fair. There is a message that
no es justo Yo hay un mensaje que me me
my son sent me and he says Look at this girl
mandó mi hijo me dice Mira esta chica
Sugu Susana Sugu Susana thinks that I
sugu Susana sugu Susana piensa que yo
'm an [ __ ] we're not going to say
soy un tampoco vamos a decir
that she's wrong and we have a
que se equivoca y tenemos una ideología
very different political ideology surely according to
política muy diferente seguramente según
her that when she's 15 years older she's going to
ella que cuando tenga 15 años más va a
be like me she's going to think the same because
ser como yo va a pensar lo mismo porque
when it's your turn it's your turn but there it
cuando te toca te toca pero ahí te
shows you that there are people who have grown up with
demuestra que hay gente que ha crecido
[ __ ] like you, like
gilipolleces en la cabeza como tú como
me and like everyone else. I saw the message
yo y como todo el mundo yo vi el mensaje
from this girl that she thinks that I'm
de esta chica que ella piensa que yo es
an [ __ ] I think she's an
un Yo pienso que es una
[ __ ] but I'm very happy and I
pero me alegro muchísimo y le
appreciate the message that she sent me She
agradezco el mensaje que que mandó me lo
sent it to me My son sent it to me and I said [ __ ]
mandó Me lo mandó mi hijo y dije
look at you and that's something to be grateful for. That's what I'm
fíjate tú y eso es de agradecer con eso
left with from all of this because people
me quedo de todo esto porque la gente
understand that I  I can get along badly with
entienda eso yo me puedo llevar mal con
that girl who also doesn't eh but I really appreciate
esa chica que tampoco eh pero agradezco
that because it shows you that she is a
mucho eso porque te demuestra que es
person and it is very important to be a person
persona y es muy importante ser persona
and she is young. And it means that there are people
y es joven Y quiere decir que hay gente
who may think very differently from you but
que puede pensar muy diferente a ti pero
call a spade a spade and wine wine.
al pan pan y al vino vino